[BRIGHT MUSIC PLAYING]
- Hey!
Hey! Hey! My bag!
Previously on
You're My Favorite Song...
You're crazy, Calix!
There! Someone took my bag,
Zion.
[OBJECTS CLATTER]
- Wait! Wait!
- Where are you going?
- Just wait!
- Where are you go...
Why did you destroy our resort?
Yes.
[XAVI THUDS]
Dad!
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Dad, Dad!
My child.
Dad.
My grandfather Xavi
is in the hospital, Zion.
[ZION GRUNTS]
- Angel, run now, hurry!
- Hey! Let go of me! Hey!
- Angel, run.
- Move aside!
- Let go of me!
- Angel, hurry!
The person who bought that
is someone dear to you.
Who?
Your wife.
Happy anniversary.
Are you having an affair
with Tyrone?
Is that really how low
you think of me?
You think I'm having an
affair with my driver?
♪ 'Cause baby,
you are my favorite song ♪
♪ I'll put you on repeat
all night ♪
♪ I know I'll never move on ♪
♪ My first,
right where I belong ♪
♪ You are my first
heartbeat song ♪
Gino.
Sir, do we have somewhere to go?
- I'll get the car.
- No, no, Gino.
You're loyal to me, right?
Of course, Sir.
I've been with you
for a long time.
I want you to follow my wife.
Watch her movements closely.
See if she's doing anything
behind my back.
Okay, Sir.
All right.
[MELLOW MUSIC PLAYING]
[XAVI COUGHING]
Grandfather.
Grandfather Xavi, how are you?
Are you having trouble
breathing?
[CLICKS TONGUE]
Don't worry, my dear,
your grandfather
is still strong.
You know,
the only thing
I'm worried about is
who those
thugs were who destroyed
our resort.
Do you know that
because of them,
our grand opening was ruined.
Dad.
Stop thinking about the resort
for now.
What matters now is that
you get better.
I'll handle everything.
I'll double my live selling of
turon so we can get more orders.
Mom Bebe, I'll help.
I'll find a way to earn money.
Oh, child, no need.
Don't worry about it.
Mom Bebe can handle it.
I'll take care of everything.
What matters is you focus on
your studies.
I'll handle everything,
okay?
There you go.
See? That's what
I've been saying.
You're just getting stressed.
We might as well
just go home.
Didn't the doctor say
I still have a year left?
Then let's go home
- and stop wasting money.
- Grandfather,
- what are you saying?
- [BEBE SIGHS HEAVILY]
You always talk like that.
It's like you're so eager
to leave us.
Don't you want to be with us?
It's not like that, my dear.
You know me,
I just don't want
to be a burden to you.
Grandfather Xavi,
you're not a burden to us.
You will never be a burden
to those who love you.
That's why we're fixing
the resort, right?
You even made me a promise.
You said you'd undergo
chemotherapy
once Gran Vista starts
earning well.
I know you want to see
grandmother in heaven,
but Mom Bebe and I
are still here.
Stay here with us for now, okay?
I'm sorry, my dear.
Sometimes I forget
how much you love me.
You're right,
[EXHALES DEEPLY]
I need to get stronger first.
Then we'll grow Gran Vista
and...
I'll get treatment.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, my dear.
Group hug.
["YOU'RE MY FAVORITE SONG"
INSTRUMENTAL]
I'm sorry, my child.
♪ Feelings inside my chest ♪
♪ Rising up ♪
♪ to my throat ♪
♪ If I say it out loud ♪
♪ Will you listen? ♪
♪ Or should I just keep
my mouth shut? ♪
Angel?
I'm not Angel.
I'm sorry.
Thank you.
Zion.
Thank you for helping
me escape yesterday.
But Grandfather Xavi,
needs surgery.
Wait did Calix beat you up?
I fought back a bit?
I mean,
I did land a punch on Poncy,
but it didn't matter,
there were too many of them,
they ganged up on me.
Come on, let's go to the clinic.
Angel, it's fine.
It might just
make things worse.
I'll just tell Ma'am Dragona...
I don't know, that I fell down
the stairs?
That I hit my head?
Right?
Are you sure?
Yeah, I'm fine.
Did I hear my name?
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Ma'am Dragona, no.
We weren't talking about you.
Angel,
come to my office.
I need to talk to you and Calix.
Yes, Ma'am.
Oh no!
Could this be because
of what happened yesterday?
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Calix and I might get expelled.
Oh no.
Now, Angel.
Wait. Yes, Ma'am.
[SOFT TENSE MUSIC]
Ma'am Dragona...
what happened yesterday,
Calix was the one
who started it.
I'll explain everything.
What happened yesterday?
Do it, Calix.
Punch her.
- Hey!
Hey!
- My bag!
- For three!
- Angel, run now, hurry!
- Hey! Let go of me!
- Hey! Angel, run!
- Move aside!
Ah, Ma'am Dragona...
why did you call us here?
I was just about to review
for the Regional Quizcon
tomorrow.
That's exactly why you're here.
Calix, your partner, Frida,
cannot join you
at the Quizcon tomorrow
because she's in the hospital.
And that's the reason
why you are here, Angel.
I want you to be Calix's
new partner
for the Regional Quizcon...
which will be happening
tomorrow.
Regional Quizcon, Ma'am?
And it's already tomorrow?
Yes.
I know it's crunch time
for review...
but because of your outstanding
performance in this school,
I have enough faith in you.
Don't you dare accept this.
If you do,
I'll make your life hell.
I don't want you as my partner.
Okay.
Well, the prize money will be
35,000 pesos.
And if you win, you'll split it
between the two of you.
I'll handle everything.
I'll double my live selling
of turon so we get more orders.
Mama Bebe, I'll help.
I'll find a way to earn money.
I accept, Ma'am Dragona.
[STIRRING MUSIC]
Very good.
Last year, Brighton Bay Academy
won the Regional Quizcon.
And according to the organizers,
the games this year will be
different
and much more difficult.
Okay?
So I'll leave the two of you
to review, okay?
And you're both excused
from all your classes today.
Okay? So you can focus
on reviewing.
- All right.
- Yes. Thank you, Ma'am.
Okay.
Thank you so much,
Ma'am Dragona.
[TENSE MUSIC]
You heard Ma'am Dragona,
let's start reviewing.
Fine.
I'll ask first.
Question number one...
why do you have the nerve
to agree to be my partner?
If you hadn't come
to Brighton Bay Academy,
someone else would've been
assigned to me.
So why don't you just quit?
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
I don't want you as a partner
either, Calix.
Do you think I want someone like
you-self-centered,
narcissistic, annoying,
and entitled-as a partner?
But I need this...
so even if your attitude
is terrible,
I'll put up with you, Calix.
You talk too much.
Stay out of my way
at the Quizcon tomorrow.
I can win the Quizcon
even on my own.
You're so arrogant.
You can do this, Angel.
[BRIGHT MUSIC]
Do this for Grandfather Xavi.
Oh no, my bag.
You're crazy, Calix!
Calix is really insane,
he hung my bag up here.
[ANGEL GRUNTING]
If it's okay with you,
I can lift you up.
["UNANG PAG-IBIG" BY
HEATH, CLIFFORD, AND MARCO]
You seem familiar.
Yup, it's me, Angel.
- ♪ How have you been? ♪
- [MIGUEL CHUCKLES]
♪ Are you still there? ♪
♪ It's been so long
since we last met ♪
♪ Do you still remember the... ♪
What are you doing here in
Solmera City?
My family and I live here now.
Really?
You might just be making
that up
maybe you're actually a stalker.
Hey, no way.
This is my father's hometown.
[LAUGHS]
Just kidding.
I thought we'd never see each
other again.
I thought so too.
Did you miss me?
- ♪ Walking home together ♪
- As a friend.
- ♪ Not in a hurry ♪
- [ANGEL CHUCKLES]
Of course, as a friend,
I missed you.
I also missed listening
to your songs.
Have you written a lot
of new songs again?
Yeah, I'll play some for you.
But
let's get your bag first.
- ♪In case it comes back to me♪
- Let's get it.
- ♪ The first... ♪
- I got you.
Don't worry, Angel.
[LAUGHS]
Let's get it.
- Wait, there, there over there.
- ♪ of fading away ♪
- ♪ The first love... ♪
- Can you carry me too?
Wait, me.
- Your head is just too big.
- ♪ I'll just whisper it ♪
♪ To the wind ♪
[GUITAR STRUMMING]
That's beautiful.
Thank you.
It's my new song...
but it's still not quite
there yet.
I'm still figuring it out.
You know,
I think you'll make it big.
Like Miguel from Siklab.
Are you a fan of Siklab?
Just a bit.
My classmates are bigger fans.
Their songs are good too but...
I like your original songs more.
My dad is...
he's very controlling.
He takes creative control
of my work.
Sorry, what was that?
Nothing, it's nothing.
It's nothing.
I just said thank you
for appreciating my songs.
Oh, here.
Sorry, my budget's a bit tight,
so this is all I could get.
It's a thank-you for your help.
Thank you.
This is my favorite.
But I can't eat this right now.
You know I can't show you
my face.
You're really something?
All right then.
I'll go along with your thing,
Captain Serenade,
just so you'll eat that.
I won't look while you eat,
promise.
Promise?
No peeking.
Yes, here I go.
["UNANG PAG-IBIG" BY
HEATH, CLIFFORD, AND MARCO]
How have you been?
Are you still there?
It's been so long
since we last met...
- Do you still remember?
- Thank you.
And good luck
with your Quizcon tomorrow,
the one you mentioned.
Thank you.
I hope we win even though...
Calix is like an unpredictable
variable in an equation.
You don't know if he'll help
- or just cause trouble.
- Always side by side...
I'm sure you'll win.
You're smart.
And I believe in you.
Sorry you can't eat.
Want me to feed you?
Okay, I'm kind of hungry too.
Open your mouth.
Thank you.
In case it comes back to me...
You're only seventeen,
it's like you threw your life
away.
Fine, fine!
If I threw it away, then I did!
You should have been the one
' who died...
instead of Mom who loved me.
Hey.
Hey, what are you doing?
Someone might see us here.
Don't overthink it.
I know you missed this too.
I feel like I recognize
that boy over there.
I think he's one of the ones
who destroyed our resort.
I think I know them.
Kaila, do you know where I can
find them?
I need to know their reason
why they destroyed our resort
or if someone ordered them
to do it.
[PEOPLE CHEERING]
If you're really nervous,
you can just stay quiet.
"Which branch of mathematics
is considered...
the 'queen of mathematics'?"
I'm not sure but...
I think it's number theory?
I think it's number theory too.
["YOU'RE MY FAVORITE SONG"
BY PRINCESS ALIYAH]